Guide to the Wayne S. Vucinich Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2006-074
  - Group 2: Radine - sources, notes, and some typescript drafts, 1926-83
    - Bileca (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bileca (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Chapter X Kotun, 3/3/75 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Chapter XIII leisure (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Church and religion (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Dress, profanity, customs (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Frescoes in the Bileca region (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fruits and vegetables (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - General: village (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - History: medieval, ancient, Trebinjc, roads (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Human loses in Rudine 1941-45 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Medicine (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous notes: WSV, (beginning April 28, 1975) (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Orah: Medieval history (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Religion (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Rudine, Bileca (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Rudine: communist politics (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Rudine: dance, music, dress (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Rudine – Ekhan (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Rudine: interwar (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Rudine: maps (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Rudine: medicinal and industrial plants, etc. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Rudine: miscellaneous articles (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Rudine: miscellaneous articles, maps, notes (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Rudine: music (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Rudine: sketches (drawings of archeological site and items with a memo and letter regarding the joint Stanford-Yugoslav Archaeological Expedition in the Trebisnjica Basin, 1969) (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Rudine: social customs, nicknames (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Serbian church and Christianization (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - WSV manuscripts (contains only illustrations), July 11, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - World War bibliography – general (with annotations) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Group 3: Trebisnjica Archaeological Expedition papers
    - Marian Wenzel, Ornamental Motifs on Tombstones from Medieval Bosnia and Surrounding Regions (1965 book) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Bileca Rudine miscellaneous materials (maps, illustrations, notes) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Preliminary reports by Judy Redfield (Mistihalj Mediaeval Cemetery Preliminary Report, May 1989 and Stanford-Yugoslav Trebisnjica Project Preliminary Report, July 1989) (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Serbians in America, miscellaneous materials (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Rudine – photos and illustrations (originals and copies) (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Notes, Vucinich's letters and a report to the Smithsonian, and clippings, 1968-69 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Arheoloski Projekt Trebisnjica (Trebisnjica Archeological Project and photodocumentary report) [maps/plans accompanying this report are in map case storage; original report removed due to fragile paper] (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Cepelica (1 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Cepelica (2 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Photographs: Cepelica (3 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographs: Cepelica (4 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Photographs: Panik (1 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Photographs: Panik (2 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Photographs: Panik (3 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Photographs: Panik (4 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Photographs: Panik (5 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Panik (6 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Photographs: Panik (7 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Photographs: Panik (8 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Panik (9 of 9) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Photographs: Orah (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Photographs: Orah (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Photographs: Orah (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Photographs: Panik, group 2 (1 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Photographs: Panik, group 2 (2 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Photographs: Panik, group 2 (3 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Photographs: Panik, group 2 (4 of 4) (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Photographs: Dzivan (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Photographs: Orah, group 2 (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Photographs: Orah, group 2 (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Photographs: Orah, group 2 (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Photographs: Oldena (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Photographs: archeological dig, misc. (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Photographs: archeological dig, misc. (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Photographs: archeological dig, misc. (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Illustrations prepared for publication (Box 10 os, Folder 1)
    - Oversize photos – medieval necropol Mistihalj (Box 10 os, Folder 2)
    - Oversize photos – Roman villa at Panik (Box 10 os, Folder 3)
    - Oversize photos – archeological, miscellaneous (Box 10 os, Folder 4)
    - maps/plans from the Trebisnjica Archeological Project report (in Box 8) (Box Map case:)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2010-143
  - Biographical/Career, Subseries 1
    - WSV Curriculum Vitae (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - WSV biography (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Wartime service in London (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Life in London (Chapter 1) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cooperation with British (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Report from London, Nov. 12 1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Stanford teaching (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Mihailovich-Tito Conflict, 1944-1945 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bileca: OSS in Washington (Ensign) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - WSV in Bari, Italy, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - World War I: London to Bari (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Service in War (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Bronze Star (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Yugoslav resistance movements (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Bulgaria: Robert Wolff versus Vucinich, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Recalled to Washington (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - WSV: Departure for America, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - WSV: Publicity, 1970s-1980s (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - U.S. War Refugee Board, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Vucinich: Awards, Prizes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - WSV: Newspaper Clippings, 1950s-1960s (Box 1, Folder 22-24)
    - Czech, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - WSV: Letters of Recommendation for WSV for Hoover Curator position, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Navy 1943- (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Vucinich, CIA: Mecca of Spies (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Case against Vucinich (Box 1, Folder 29-32)
    - Freedom of Information documents from binder, 1944-1980 (Box 1, Folder 33-34)
  - Writing and Research, Subseries 2
    - Bulgarian Resistance Documents (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - McDowell Report (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Poruka (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Dig" Publicity, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Bileca-Harnessing Trebisnjica (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Wenzel, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Stecici Shipment, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Progress Reports, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Trebisnjica Project Proposals, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Zimmerman, DeClercq, 1967 fall (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Smithsonian 1, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Smithsonian 2, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Smithsonian 3, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ehrich, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Coup 1941 / Poruka (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - unlabeled (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Architecture (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bileca Clan (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bileca: Early Inhabitants (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bileca-Death (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Bileca: Education (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Bileca-Economy (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Bileca Emigres (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Depression (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - History: Origin of the Family through the Break up of the Extended Family (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Bileca - Diet (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Extended Family (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Assistants over the Years (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - My Life (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Historical Bileca Background Introduction (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bileca-Intro/Tragedy (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Childhood Memories (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bileca Profiles/Non Vucinich (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Bileca-Acculturation (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Bileca-Hearth (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bileca-Plans for WSV's Future (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bileca Recreation Includes "Toasts" (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bileca-Life There (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Bileca-Leaving Home "Breakdown of Collective Existence" (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bileca-Inheritance Lost (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Bileca-Reminices and Return Home (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Bileca-Genealogy (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bileca-Marriage and Wedding (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Katun (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bileca-Social Change (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Bileca-Vucinich Family Profiles (includes mention of Pranko Kebeljic) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Bileca-Police (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Baba Adzich, Andja Bjeletich (Profiles) (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - St. George (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Profiles: Perun (see also Wilmington and Sijelo) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bileca-Music (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Vladimir Corovic (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Bileca-Language (Billy Goat) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Epic Poetry (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bileca-Death (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Bileca-Slava (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Bileca Peasant Attributes (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Bileca-Religion (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Early History-Mountain Life (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Bicela-Religion and rites of passage (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Bileca-School Friends (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bileca Schools (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Folk Medicine (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Bileca-Women (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Bileca Tuberculosis (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Tranhumance Article (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Transhumance-The Passing of an Era (Serb World) Orphans Arrived (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Bileca Political Participation (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Bileca-Transportation (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Bileca-World War I (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Bileca Zadruga (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Bileca Mountain Life (See also Transhumance) (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Bileca Transhumance after WWII (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bileca Transhumance (Mt. Life Folder 2) (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Sijelo (explanation of Ring game) (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Misc. (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Vojislav Gacinovic (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Definition of Rudine and Dubrovnik (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Formation of Yugoslavia Geography (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - B/R Origins (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Early Writings on Bileca Rudine Explanation of Importance (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Questionnaire (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Orah in Rudine (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Bileca Rudine -Short Review (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Bileca: Where is Bileca Rudine? (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - History or Bosnia Hercegovina before 1878 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - History: Feudal Land System-Origin of Vucinich Family Ottoman (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bileca Animals inc. horse (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - B/R Monument Museum (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bileca-Antiquity (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bileca-Army (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bileca Austrian Occupation (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Extended Family after Austro-Hungarian Occupation] (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bileca-Baptismal (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bileca-Battle of Kosovo (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Bileca-Works in Progress ("Origin of the name Rudine" in Thesis Statement folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Bileca-Berkeley including teacher and student profiles (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Bileca Berkeley post-Prague (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Bogumils (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Bosnian History Bogumils mentioned (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Bileca Church (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bileca C"itaonica (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Bileca Homelands and Homeland History Neighbor States Oppose Creation of Yugo (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - House in Bileca (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Bileca City Planning andn Gov't (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Bileca Clothing (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Bileca Communism (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Bileca Cominform Expulsion (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Early Abodes (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Dig 1967 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Bileca Epic Poetry (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bileca Ethnogenesis Origins of Vlachs and others and Bogumils (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Bileca (WSV's) Family Split same info as in Family Profiles (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Bileca Flora Fauna (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Glasniks (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Bileca Hajduks/Uskoks (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Bileca Grazing Land (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Bileca Holidays/Christmas (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Bileca Holidays misc. (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Bileca Humnina (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Industrial Plant Tobacco (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Bileca Immigrants in LA post '32 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Bileca Inserts (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Bileca Intra Family Relations (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Karst Region (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Bileca: Islamization (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Bileca Katun (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Immigration Sifkartas Ship-ticket providers (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Bileca Katun Folder 1 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Bileca Katun Folder 2 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Bileca Komiti (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Bileca Komiti 2 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Bileca Konavli (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Kosovo (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Bileca Land (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Bileca Lager (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bileca Language Older Version (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bileca Melting Pot (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Military Recruitment Law (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Bileca Mlada Bosna (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Montenegro (Inc. Proclamation of Union) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Monuments (early) (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bileca Modern Music (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Bileca Music Gusle (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Yugoslav Music: Songs (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Bileca Muslims (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Bileca Ottoman Rule (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Bileca Pastures (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Bileca Orah (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Bileca Politics (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bileca Politics and Redemption (Serb) (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Bileca Population (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Serbs, Muslims and Croats (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Schutzkorps (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Slava Cont'd (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Bileca Starina Novak (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Bileca Statistics (inserts) 1920s-1930s (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Bileca Statistics (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Bileca Taxation (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Titles of Rules and Territorial Units (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bileca Political History (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Bileca Transhumance/Mount. Life Folder (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Bileca Travunija (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Trebisnjica (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bileca Tribe (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Bileca Undivided Lands (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Bileca Vila (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Union of Montenegro and Serbia (and just Montenegro) (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Bileca Villages (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Bileca Villages Cooperation (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Bileca Zavala Monastery (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Bileca Vlachs (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Inter-War Period 1918-1939 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Pastoral Life Post WWII (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Bileca and WWII (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - WWII and family (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Yugoslavia's Way to Socialism '44-'48 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Bileca: Trebinje '01 and older version (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Bileca Proletarian Days (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Extended Fmaily following WWII (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Bileca-Changes after WWII (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Bileca WWII and after (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - WSV Service in London WWII (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Summary 1944-1953 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Bileca Food and Mealtime Revisited (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Travunijia/Trebinje (History) Acculturation Assimilation (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Trebinje Exploration (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Diet 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Barbershop 1960s (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Bileca Visit Alumni Summary of Life and Conditions 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 1969: Post Dig (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Acculturation culled (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Alumni (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Decline of the extended family after WWI (Rade p52) Old version Ivan/Rade extended family (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Kinship (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Emigres (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Marriage and Weddings (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Schools and Literacy/Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Stys, Konstanty (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Binder with correspondence: Berkeley, State Department, WSV application letters to various universities for faculty positions (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Background (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Introduction-culled (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Transhumance (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Transhumance-culled (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Krsto (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Serb Community in Wilmington (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Krsna Slava binder (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Krsna Slava binder (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Topography and Map (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Albanian Linguistic Inference (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Policy 1878-1903 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Bileca-Austrian Rule (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Austro-Hungarian Occupation (Chapter 3) (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Serbia and Montenegro (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Bileca-Austrian Rule/Kallay (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Remembrances of Ancestral Home (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - King Nikola (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Soviet Nationalities (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Bileca-Austrian Rule/Occupation (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Heroes of WWII (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Footnotes, Introduction (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 3 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 4 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 6 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 7 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 8 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 9 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 10 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 12 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Footnotes, Chapter 13 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Footnotes, Misc. (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Outlines (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Bileca contents, outline versions (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Bileca outlines/file directories (Box 7, Folder 16-17)
    - Binder contents lists (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Binder 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Binder 2 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Binder 3 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Binder 4 (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
    - Binder 5 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Binder 6 (Box 7, Folder 25-27)
    - Binder 11 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Binder 12 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Binder 16 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Binder 18 (Bileca Rudine VI-XII) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Binder 19 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Binder 21 (Box 8, Folder 5-7)
    - Binder 22 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Binder 23 (Box 8, Folder 9-11)
    - Binder 24 (Box 8, Folder 12-14)
    - Binder 25 (Bileca II: food, rites) (Box 8, Folder 15-17)
    - Binder 26 (Bileca III) (Box 8, Folder 18-20)
    - Binder 27 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Binder 30 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Binder 31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Binder 32 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Binder 34 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Binder 35 (Bileca Rudine) (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Binder, Bileca-Service in Bulgaria (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Trebisnjica Archaeological Expedition, Subseries 3
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Panik-Crkvina (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Kolanjevici (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Omedjimne (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Vrelo Tresisnjice, Crkvina Ruzica, Nekropola (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Cepelica Tumulusi (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Orah Crkvina (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Projekat Trebisnjica, Misrihatj, Srednjovjekovna, Nekropola (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2011-202
  - Vucinich, Alexander, obituaries, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Office of Strategic Services Pocket Guide to Yugoslavia, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ethical Diffusion of Serbs, documentation and maps for the London Conference on Yugoslavia, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Smithsonian (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sebian Orthodox Church, history of (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Political Currents among Immigrant Serbs in California on the Eve of the Insurrections of 1875, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Non-Russian Nationalities, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bulgaria (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Yugoslav Movement (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Novichey (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Maps (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photocopied research materials, mostly Cyrillic (Serbian?) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Serbian newspapers (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Serbia news clippings (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Slovo newspapers (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers (likely Serbian) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Croatian intellectuals in Yugoslavia, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Declassified documents re Office of Strategic Services position / Bulgaria (photocopies from National Archives), 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Review of International Affairs, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Reprints and publications (by others, non-English) (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Unidentified documents (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Mistihalj Nadgrobne Ploce I Skeliti (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Photographs, Mistihalj Stecci (Box 3, Folder 4-5)
  - Photographs, Orah Tumulusi (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Panik (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs from unlabeled box (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
  - Collapse of Austria-Hungary, roundtable discussion at Stanford, 1966 Apr 15; 2 audiotape(s) (reel-to-reel) (Box 4)
- Class Roll Books, 1946-1955; Accession ARCH-2011-527 (Box 1)
  Restricted 75 years from date.